rebelcircus.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy

**  Last Updated: May 24, 2018**

PRIVACY POLICY/YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information Sell It Social, llc. and its retail brand Rebel Circus (collectively, “RebelCircus”) collect from and about you when you you (1)  visit a Rebel Circus website (a “Site”). (2) interact with us offline, by telephone (an “Offline Activity”). The Site and Offline Events are collectively referred to as the “Services.” This Privacy Policy also explains how RebelCircus may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it. By using the Services, you agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy, and agree to the RebelCircus Terms of Use, which are incorporated by reference. If you do not agree, please do not access or use the Services.

1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

Information You Provide to Us

RebelCircus collects information from you when you choose to share it with us. This may include when you use the Services; register or create an account; enroll in one of our loyalty programs; maintain a “wish list”; purchase products or services; request information from us; sign up for our newsletters or email list; enter a contest, sweepstakes or other promotion; fill out a survey; request customer support; or otherwise communicate with or contact us. The information we collect may include your name, physical address, email address, telephone or mobile phone number, date of birth/age, gender, RebelCircus account user name and password, and photograph.

You may also provide us with certain information in connection with specification transactions: 

• Information You Provide When You Make a Purchase. If you make a purchase from us, we collect a credit/debit card number and related financial information (such as CVV, expiration date, and billing address.) 

• Information You Provide about a Third Party. If you send someone else a communication through the Sites or Apps, such as an invitation to a friend, the information you provide (e.g., name, e-mail address) will be used to facilitate the communication and will not be used for any other marketing purpose, unless such person registers with us or becomes a customer, we obtain consent from such person, or we explicitly say otherwise at the point of collection. 

• Information You Provide Through Social Media. We may also give you the option to link to your Facebook or other social media account through a Site or App. When you do, we may automatically receive certain information about you based on your registration and privacy settings on those third-party services. This may include, but may not be limited to, your name, user name, demographic information, updated address or contact information, location, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and online activity. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users give us access to their accounts, and information about you (such as the fact that you are “friends”) is otherwise accessible through those accounts. 

Information Automatically Collected

We may use a variety of technologies such as cookies, web beacons, embedded scripts, or other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to, and users of, our Sites and Apps and interactions with our emails and online and mobile advertisements, and to allow RebelCircus to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information.   
For example, we may automatically collect certain information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, device type and model, operating system, unique device identifier of any of your computer(s) or device(s) that are used to access a Site or App, software version, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, geolocation, preferred language, and the domain name from which you accessed a Site or App. We also may collect information about your use of the Sites and Apps, including the date and time you visit a Site or App, the areas or pages of a Site or App that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using a Site or App, your GPS location (if you have enabled location tracking on your device), the number of times you return to a Site or App, other click-stream or site usage data, emails that you open, forward, or click-through to a Site or App, and other sites that you may visit.   
• Third-Party Service Providers. We may use third-party service providers to support our Sites or Apps. Some of these service providers may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, Flash cookies, embedded scripts, or HTML5 cookies to receive, collect, and store information.   
• Third-Party Analytic Technologies. We may use third parties’ analytics and tracking tools to better understand who is using the Sites or Apps, how people are using the Sites or Apps, how to improve the effectiveness of the Sites or Apps and related content, and to help us or those third parties serve more targeted advertising to you across the Internet. These tools may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, Flash cookies, embedded scripts, HTML5 cookies, or other technologies to automatically collect and store certain information. They may also combine information they collect from your interaction with the Sites or Apps with information they collect from other sources. We do not have access to, or control over, these third parties’ use of cookies or other tracking technologies. 

Information Collected From Other Sources

We may acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information that you provide or that we collect automatically (such as information to validate or update your address or other demographic and lifestyle information). We may use this information to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect, to target our communications so that we can inform you of products, services, or other offers that may be of interest to you, and for internal business analysis or other business purposes. 

Combination of Information

We may combine the information we receive from and about you, including information you provide to us and information we automatically collect through our Sites and Apps, as well as information collected offline, across other computers or devices that you may use, and from third-party sources. 

2\. HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED?

RebelCircus may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:   
· To provide you with products, information, or services that you have requested or agreed to receive, or when necessary. · To contact you with information, newsletters, and promotional materials from RebelCircus or on behalf of our third-party partners and affiliates. · To enable you to participate in a variety of Site and App features, such as sweepstakes, message boards, other communication features, user-generated content functions, and interactive features. · To process your registration and/or enrollment in any loyalty programs, including by verifying that your email address is active and valid. · To review the usage and operations of our Sites and Apps, develop new products or services, and conduct analysis to enhance or improve our content, products, and services. · To enhance your online shopping experience, including as a way to recognize you and welcome you to the Sites or Apps. · To provide you with customized content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Sites and Apps, via email, text message, or push notification, or across other websites, mobile applications, social media or online services. · To use your data in an aggregated non-specific format for analytical and demographic purposes. · To address problems with the Sites and Apps or our business, and to protect the security or integrity of the Sites and Apps and our business, · To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and prevent fraud. · As disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent. Additionally, if you use the Sites or Apps to connect with third-party services, you authorize us to use information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third-party services based on your requests. 

3\. HOW AND WHEN DO WE DISCLOSE INFORMATION?

We may share the information we collect from and about you in the following ways: • Service Providers: We may share your information with third-party service providers that provide business, professional, or technical support functions for us (including to the extent necessary or desirable to fulfill or ship your order or complete your transaction), help us operate our business and the Sites and Apps, or administer activities on our behalf. We do not authorize these third-party service providers to use or disclose your information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements.   
• Co-Branded Relationships: Certain areas of our Sites and Apps may be provided to you in association with third parties, such as advertisers that provide products and services or rewards programs.   
• Sweepstakes, Contests, and Other Promotions. If you choose to enter one of our promotions, we may disclose your information to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of the promotion, as required by law, as otherwise permitted by the promotion’s official rules, or otherwise in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.   
• Select Third Parties: We may share your information with our select partners, affiliates (including affiliates that do and do not bear the Rebel Circus brand name), and other third parties that we believe may have offers of interest to you.   
• Legal Matters; Safety: We may access and disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, judicial processes, or government requests and investigations, or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law. We may disclose your information to protect the security of our Sites and Apps, servers, network systems, and databases. We also may disclose your information as necessary, if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Use, any other legal document or contract related to our services, or the rights of any third party.   
• Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets: We may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use information provided through the Sites and Apps in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.   
• Aggregate or Anonymous Non-Personal Information: We may share aggregate, anonymous, or de-identified non-personal information with third parties for their marketing or analytics uses.   
• Other: We also may share your information as disclosed to you at the time of collection. 

4\. YOUR CHOICES AND OPT-OUTS

Cookies, Tracking Options, and California Do Not Track Disclosures

Certain parts of our Sites and Apps require cookies. You are free to set your browser or operating system settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Sites or Apps or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more information on how to delete and/or disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences.   
Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. We may use cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to link data collected across other computers or devices that you may use.   
To learn more about the use of cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to know your choices with respect to collection and use of the data by these third party tools, you may visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (NAI) opt-out page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices. To opt-out of the use of your mobile device ID for targeted advertising, please see http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices. If you wish to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, Google has developed the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available here. On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising. 

Opt Out Preferences

We provide our customers with the opportunity to opt out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to placement, processing, fulfillment, or delivery of a product or service. To opt-out of marketing communications, you may use one of these convenient methods:   
• Electronic Promotional Offers. If you do not want to receive marketing emails from us click the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email. You may also opt-out of receiving emails from us by sending us an email at info@rebelcircus.com with “Do Not Email” in the subject line.   
Your instructions to limit the use of your information for these purposes will be processed as soon as reasonably practicable. Additionally, we are not responsible for informing third parties (including without limitation our third-party service providers or partners) with whom we have already shared your personal information of any changes requested pursuant to this section. 

Access to Your Information

You can verify, correct, or update certain information associated with your Site or App account. You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of this information. If you choose to deactivate your account, we may still retain certain information for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, enforce our Terms of Use or other policies, take actions we deem necessary due to technical and legal requirements, and as dictated by constraints related to the security, integrity, and operation of our Sites and Apps. 

5\. YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS - UPDATING, OBTAINING A COPY, OR DELETING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If the law grants you such rights, you may ask to access, correct, or delete your personal information that is stored in our systems. You may also ask for our confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data.

Subject to the limitations in law, you may request that we update, correct, or delete inaccurate or outdated information. You may also request that we suspend the use of any personal data whose accuracy you contest while we verify the status of that data.

Subject to law, you may also be entitled to obtain the personal data you directly provided us (excluding data we obtained from other sources) in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and may have the right to transmit the data to another party.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, contact us at: [info@rebelcircus.com](mailto:info@rebelcircus.com). When handling these requests,

 we may ask for additional information to confirm your identity and your request. You must put the statement “Updating my personal information” in the subject field. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information. Non-affiliated third parties are independent from Rebel Circus, and if you wish to receive information about your disclosure choices or stop communications from such third parties, you will need to contact those non-affiliated third parties directly.

6\. THIRD-PARTY CONTENT, LINKS, AND PLUG-INS

The Sites and Apps may have links to third-party websites and mobile applications, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the practices of such sites and apps. The Sites and Apps may also offer you the ability to interact with social plugins from social media sites, which may allow us and/or the social media site to receive data from or about you. In some cases, we may know that you clicked on a social plugin, such as a Twitter Follow button, or receive other information from the social media sites. Similarly, if you have previously provided personal information to a third party operating a plug-in on the Sites or Apps, then such third party may recognize you on the Sites or Apps. Your use of social network plugins is subject to each social media site’s privacy policy, which may be different from ours, so please read those policies carefully to understand their policies and your options. As with linked sites, we have no control over the information that is collected, stored, or used by social network plugins, and are not responsible for the practices of such sites. 

7\. PUBLIC FORUMS

Any information you may disclose on our Sites or Apps, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on the Sites or Apps or other third-party websites that the Sites or Apps may link to, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. 

8\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Protecting children’s privacy is important to us. We do not direct the Sites or Apps to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen. If Rebel Ciurcus learns that a child under the age of thirteen has provided personally identifiable information to a Site or App, it will use reasonable efforts to remove such information from its files. 

9\. DATA SECURITY

We have taken certain physical, administrative, and technical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Services users. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures. When you provide sensitive information (such as credit card information) via the Sites or Apps, we encrypt the transmission of that information using transport layer security technology (TLS). 

10\. DATA STORAGE

Your personal information may be stored on servers in the United States and is subject to the laws of the United States, where the data protection and other laws may differ from those of other countries. Your personal information may be disclosed in response to inquiries or requests from government authorities or to respond to judicial process in the countries in which we operate.

    11. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

12\. REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, remove, or otherwise revise portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Sites and Apps. Your continued use of the Sites and Apps following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. If we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. 

13\. HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at info@RebelCircus.com, 311 w43rd street, 12th floor, New York, NY, 10038, USA or 6464309351

LIST OF COOKIES WE COLLECT

 The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name

| 

COOKIE Description  
  
---|---  
  
CART

| 

The association with your shopping cart.  
  
CATEGORY_INFO

| 

Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
  
COMPARE

| 

The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
  
CURRENCY

| 

Your preferred currency  
  
CUSTOMER

| 

An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
  
CUSTOMER_AUTH

| 

An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
  
CUSTOMER_INFO

| 

An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS

| 

Stores the Customer Segment ID  
  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE

| 

A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
  
FRONTEND

| 

You sesssion ID on the server.  
  
GUEST-VIEW

| 

Allows guests to edit their orders.  
  
LAST_CATEGORY

| 

The last category you visited.  
  
LAST_PRODUCT

| 

The most recent product you have viewed.  
  
NEWMESSAGE

| 

Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
  
NO_CACHE

| 

Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART

| 

A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
  
POLL

| 

The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
  
POLLN

| 

Information on what polls you have voted on.  
  
RECENTLYCOMPARED

| 

The items that you have recently compared.  
  
STF

| 

Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
  
STORE

| 

The store view or language you have selected.  
  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE

| 

Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS

| 

The products that you have recently viewed.  
  
WISHLIST

| 

An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
  
WISHLIST_CNT

| 

The number of items in your Wishlist.
